<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lodeup Engineering Blog</title>
    <description>Geolode is a service for mobile developers to simplify user-to-user interactions. The service provides geo-location and user interaction APIs to help mobile developers find and interact with nearby users  and entities.
</description>
    <link>http://engineering.lodeup.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://engineering.lodeup.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:17:01 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:17:01 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introducing Geolode - Proximity-based Interaction as a Service</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Geolode is the upcoming and first Lodeup product. It is the result of several side projects that Nic Kline and I have worked on together. We had a need, in many projects, for  service that provides geo-location storage and querying. With such a service, mobile applications can provide better social interactions based on user-to-user proximity. We want to make available this service to mobile developers, so they can continue to focus on what they do best without having to worry about writing their own geo-location service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this is an engineering blog, we would like to chronicle the overall launch of the product. In addition to technical topics, we may touch on marketing and business, as we are learning and making decisions within those realms. We would like to partner with some app developers as we flesh out the full API to make sure we are meeting a broader set of needs, rather than what was needed for our side projects. In the coming weeks, we will have a proper landing/early-access sign-up page. Meanwhile, if you are interested in partnering with us, please connect with us on twitter; (John, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/johnlcox&quot;&gt;@johnlcox&lt;/a&gt;; Nic, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nic_kline&quot;&gt;@nic_kline&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:02:56 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://engineering.lodeup.com/2015/10/14/introducing-geolode-proximity-based-interaction-as-a-service.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://engineering.lodeup.com/2015/10/14/introducing-geolode-proximity-based-interaction-as-a-service.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
